Morning
I'm kind of bummed. I my bike is not charging. I don't know if I can fix it
I ordered a new charger for it
You hear me, I'm sorry
Yeah
Good morning. Yeah, so my bike's not charging. Do you guys ever had a bike not charge?
Maybe a fake Mary just to get to the bike shop. Does he bike you care?
Otherwise a box
You know eventually they will go out, you know
I want it to last for a long time
What do you think guys? I think it'll be fixed
Sorry guys, I'm sorry about last night too
Morning should be to be
Hi guys, I'll call around 30 to see if they anyone fixes these bikes. Oh
Punchy shoes, I see you're not start crying
Someone asked what someone asked they said she said she took up the community she says she's transgender. I mean, I
Attack anybody
I
LGBTQ friendly I don't know if people say I'm attacking anybody. Good morning everybody had to be
No, I don't I didn't call her a man
There's everyone doing this morning. I'm sorry guys. I'm so
It's okay. I'm just kind of pissed. I'm like my bike's not charging right now
Last night it was a big nightmare. I got all the locked tangled in the
Gears, but I mean I was able to like get home and stuff
She's not working
Not charging
and it dies
Do you think we will fix that?
Sure, I can fix it. Okay
Okay, well, I feel I feel better. I don't know. I'll have to go to the repair store
I'd be might be a little possible little money. I ordered another charger the other charger might work
It's gonna get it's not it's not plugging in right. I don't know if it's the right one or something. Maybe it's the right one. I
Think I did was charging before though
Light is on a screen
Thank you. I face you. Let's go. Let's be positive. Let's see. You will be miracle
If you I don't know maybe it's repairable. I have a lot of do it
Yeah, we'll see maybe it'll work
Okay, well, I don't know. It's gonna say good morning and stuff
Everyone asleep
Thank you guys
Thanks guys
Take guys. Bye